<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rxjs on Martin Sundvall</title><link>https://example.com/techs/rxjs/</link><description>Recent content in rxjs on Martin Sundvall</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© Martin Sundvall</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 19:47:09 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/techs/rxjs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>vattenfall electricity my pages</title><link>https://example.com/portfolio/vattenfall-my-pages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/portfolio/vattenfall-my-pages/</guid><description>At Vattenfall me and my crossfunctional team cream created content and components for customers of electricity and content editors managing the site. The components were created as webcomponents possible to use from cms (episerver), and integrated library components to provide consistency of appearance.
Storybook was used to document and develop library components in isolation.
Angular framework was used together with jest for testing, azure for api&amp;rsquo;s, Ngxs for state management and tailwind for styling.</description></item><item><title>vattenfall login flow</title><link>https://example.com/portfolio/vattenfall-login/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/portfolio/vattenfall-login/</guid><description>As an internal project me and my team implemented the design and flow to login with bank-id.
A technical flowchart was created from the given design and was used as a tool to early on discuss aspects of both ui and api-calls. This was used by the team during the entire project and proved to be very useful. Missing parts of the flow were discovered early on and logical improvements could be done before any coding was executed.</description></item><item><title>kronofogden my pages</title><link>https://example.com/portfolio/kronofogden/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/portfolio/kronofogden/</guid><description>At Kronofogden me and my crossfunctional team cream created application flows for logged in users. As an authority the requirements of accessability were very strict.
Storybook was used to document and develop library components in isolation.
Angular framework was used together with Karma for testing, azure for api&amp;rsquo;s, Ngrx for state management and scss together with bootstrap for styling.
As a team lead I facilitated upgrade of the angular framework and configured tools for development.</description></item></channel></rss>