<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>javascript on Martin Sundvall</title><link>https://sundvall.github.io/sundvall-portfolio/techs/javascript/</link><description>Recent content in javascript on Martin Sundvall</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© Martin Sundvall</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 19:47:09 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sundvall.github.io/sundvall-portfolio/techs/javascript/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>comeon casino payment solutions</title><link>https://sundvall.github.io/sundvall-portfolio/portfolio/comeon-casino/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sundvall.github.io/sundvall-portfolio/portfolio/comeon-casino/</guid><description>I created the first frontend solution for the mobile payment solution. This was created in pure vanilla javascript and built upon the pre-redux solution of state management called &amp;lsquo;flux&amp;rsquo;. The main idéa was to separate management of data from rendering, and was solved with several &amp;lsquo;stores&amp;rsquo;. The dom-templates were handled by javascript.
When more developers joined and redux with react became popular. Thus the demand on communication grew and the application could be improved with conventional standards.</description></item><item><title>adssets e-commerce solutions</title><link>https://sundvall.github.io/sundvall-portfolio/portfolio/adssets/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2015 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sundvall.github.io/sundvall-portfolio/portfolio/adssets/</guid><description>At adssets I developed both new products for advertising and the self-service system to add content to existing ones. Everything was done in pure javascript and css and reusability was improved by combinations of command line scripts and reusable functions.
The work included both legacy formats and new development for video and animated interactive content used for advertising. Many edge-cases occured when smartphones, native apps and browsers where combined. Most often the debugging was made with remote scripts.</description></item><item><title>self-service web for workflow sofware</title><link>https://sundvall.github.io/sundvall-portfolio/portfolio/caperio/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sundvall.github.io/sundvall-portfolio/portfolio/caperio/</guid><description>At Caperio me and my team developed a new self service portal. It was an R &amp;amp; D project to provide an interface to workflow software. As part of this I added content to the nodejs api and implemented the design evolved in close collaboration with both interaction designer and backend programmers.
Challenges and technical aspects:
fullstack development pioneer project evolving design</description></item></channel></rss>