<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PORTFOLIO on Martin Sundvall</title><link>https://sundvall.github.io/sundvall-portfolio/portfolio/</link><description>Recent content in PORTFOLIO on Martin Sundvall</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© Martin Sundvall</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 19:47:09 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sundvall.github.io/sundvall-portfolio/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vattenfall electricity my pages</title><link>https://sundvall.github.io/sundvall-portfolio/portfolio/vattenfall-my-pages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sundvall.github.io/sundvall-portfolio/portfolio/vattenfall-my-pages/</guid><description>At Vattenfall me and my crossfunctional team cream created components for customers and editors.
The components were created as webcomponents possible to use from cms (episerver), and integrated library components to provide consistency of appearance.
Storybook was used to document and develop library components in isolation.
Angular framework was used together with jest for testing, azure for api&amp;rsquo;s, Ngxs for state management and tailwind for styling.
Strict adherence to naming conventions was helpful to maintain the codebase.</description></item><item><title>Vattenfall electricity login flow</title><link>https://sundvall.github.io/sundvall-portfolio/portfolio/vattenfall-login/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sundvall.github.io/sundvall-portfolio/portfolio/vattenfall-login/</guid><description>As an internal project me and my team implemented the design and flow to login with bank-id.
I introduced the creation of a visual flowchart as one of the first tasks in the agile sprint. It was created from the given ux-design and included the navigation logic and network traffic. This became the gathering point to early discuss aspects of both ui and api-calls. It also simplifed communication outside the dev-team with stakeholders and testers.</description></item><item><title>Kronofogden my pages</title><link>https://sundvall.github.io/sundvall-portfolio/portfolio/kronofogden/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sundvall.github.io/sundvall-portfolio/portfolio/kronofogden/</guid><description>At Kronofogden me and my crossfunctional team cream created application flows for logged in users. I was leading the frontend development and focused on upgrades of the technical environment and improvements in developer experience, aside from implementing accessible forms. The environment was very restricted and provided many challenges to provide access to tooling that is in most circumstances are natural.
As an authority the requirements of accessability were very strict, and an external consultancy firm was engaged to evalutate the results.</description></item><item><title>Comeon casino payment solutions</title><link>https://sundvall.github.io/sundvall-portfolio/portfolio/comeon-casino/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sundvall.github.io/sundvall-portfolio/portfolio/comeon-casino/</guid><description>I created the first frontend solution for the mobile payment solution. This was created in pure vanilla javascript and built upon the pre-redux solution of state management called &amp;lsquo;flux&amp;rsquo;. The main idéa was to separate management of data from rendering, and was solved with several &amp;lsquo;stores&amp;rsquo;. The dom-templates were handled by javascript.
When more developers joined and redux with react became popular the first solution was transferred into this. During the rewrite the system was documented with flowcharts.</description></item><item><title>Adssets e-commerce solutions</title><link>https://sundvall.github.io/sundvall-portfolio/portfolio/adssets/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2015 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sundvall.github.io/sundvall-portfolio/portfolio/adssets/</guid><description>At adssets I developed both new products for advertising and the self-service system to add content to existing ones. Everything was done in pure javascript and css and reusability was improved by combinations of command line scripts and reusable functions.
The work included both legacy formats and new development for video and animated interactive content used for advertising. Many edge-cases occured when smartphones, native apps and browsers where combined. Most often the debugging was made with remote scripts.</description></item><item><title>Caperio self-service web for workflow sofware</title><link>https://sundvall.github.io/sundvall-portfolio/portfolio/caperio/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sundvall.github.io/sundvall-portfolio/portfolio/caperio/</guid><description>At Caperio me and my team developed a new self service portal. It was an R &amp;amp; D project to provide a friendly interface to workflow software. As part of this I added content to the nodejs api and implemented the design evolved in close collaboration with both interaction designer and backend programmers.
Experience:
fullstack development pioneer project evolving design</description></item></channel></rss>